fetchr.us 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy - Fetchr

##### Privacy Policy

Last Revised: February 11, 2018

MENA 360 DWC-LLC (d/b/a “ **Fetchr** ”), which includes MENA 360 DWC-LLC and its affiliates and contracted business partners (collectively, the “ **Fetchr Group Companies** ”), values you as our client and recognizes that privacy is important to you and the customers you serve. We may change this policy from time to time.  If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this policy. Changes in the Privacy Policy become effective immediately after the first posting of any revised version. To stay abreast of these changes, please regularly check our Privacy Policy. Beyond the Privacy Policy, your use of Fetchr is also subject to our Terms and Conditions (www.fetchr.us/legal).

**_Collection of Information_** ** _ _**

We want you to be familiar with how we collect, use, and disclose information.  This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of the Fetchr Group Companies in connection with information that we collect through websites, applications, and other electronic media operated by us from which you are accessing this Privacy Policy, including Fetchr.us and other websites owned or controlled by the Fetchr Group Companies (collectively, the “ **Websites** ”), through the software applications made available by us for use on or through computers and mobile devices (the “ **App** ”), through our social media pages that we control from which you are accessing this Privacy Policy (collectively, our “ **Social Media Pages** ”), through HTML-formatted email messages that we send to you that link to this Privacy Policy, and through your communications with us and when you use or benefit from our services (collectively, including the Websites, the Apps, our Social Media Pages, and all other similar electronic media (and other forms of communication) now existing and/or hereafter created the “ **Digital Platforms** ,” and together with offline channels, the “ **Services** ”).

This policy applies to any users of the Services, anywhere in the world, and to anyone else who contacts Fetchr or otherwise submits information to Fetchr, unless noted below.  **This includes those who use Fetchr Services to:**

  * Request deliveries of food or other items;
  * Provide delivery services; and,
  * Any other user of the Services (including Apps, websites, and API), and anyone else who contacts Fetchr or otherwise submits information to Fetchr, unless subject to a separate privacy policy, notice or agreement.

By providing Personal and Other Information to us (or if you are a customer of one of our clients, by providing such information to us via the client), you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

Fetchr uses the information collected via Digital Platforms to:

  * Market and improve Fetchr Services;
  * Transact business with Fetchr clients;
  * Improve the Fetchr Digital Platforms and the content distributed through them,
  * Contact you with updates to and information about the Fetchr Digital Platforms and Fetchr Services and activities, to help with fraud identification;
  * Enable features to personalize your Fetchr account, such as creating bookmarks for your favorite places;
  * Conduct other Fetchr marketing, promotional and informational activities;
  * Help Fetchr understand the efficacy of the content, messaging and information provided through the Digital Platforms;
  * Identify the type of digital and other content, messaging and information visitors to the Digital Platforms value most, assess and monitor certain user experience;
  * Investigate or address claims or disputes relating to your use of Fetchr Services, or as otherwise allowed by applicable law; and,
  * Perform other activities as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Information You Provide to Us**

We collect information you provide directly to us.  For example, we may collect information when you interact with us as a client or prospective or former client, create an account to access certain features of our Services, send us an email, fill out a form, respond to a survey, register for an event, enter a promotional drawing, or otherwise communicate with us.  The types of information we may collect include your name, postal address, email address, phone number, current occupation and business contact information, social security number, employment application information (including education and work history), LinkedIn handle, demographic information, conference/event preferences, payment method information, and any other information you choose to provide. If you decide to sign up for Fetchr using your Facebook account, we will also get basic information from your Facebook profile like your name, gender, profile photo, and Facebook friends.

**Information You Create Using Our Services**

When you access or use the Services, we automatically collect certain information created by you, including:

_Location Information_ Depending on the Fetchr services that you use and your App settings or device permissions, Fetchr may collect your precise or approximate location information as determined through data such as GPS, IP address, and WiFi. If you label certain locations, such as “Home” and “Work,” we receive that information as well. If you are a driver or delivery partner, Fetchr collects location information when the Fetchr App is running in the foreground (app open and on-screen) or background (app open but not on screen) of your device. Fetchr may collect location information when the Fetchr App is running in the foreground. In certain regions, Fetchr may also collect this information when the Fetchr App is running in the background of your device if this collection is enabled through your App settings or device permissions.

Fetchr App users may use the application without enabling Fetchr to collect their location information. However, this may affect the functionality available on your Fetchr App. For example, if you do not enable Fetchr to collect your location information, you will have to manually enter your pickup address. In addition, location information will be collected from the delivery partner during delivery, even if you have not enabled Fetchr to collect your location information.

_Transaction Information_ We collect transaction details related to your use of our Services, including the type of services you requested or provided, date and time the service was provided, amount charged, distance traveled, and other related transaction details. Additionally, if someone uses your promotion code, we may associate your name with that person.

_Address book_ If you permit the Fetchr App to access the address book on your device, we may collect names and contact information from your address book to facilitate social interactions through our services and for other purposes described in this policy or at the time of consent or collection.

_Device Information_ We may collect information about the devices you use to access our Services, including the hardware models, operating systems and versions, software, file names and versions, preferred languages, unique device identifiers, advertising identifiers, serial numbers, device motion information, mobile network information, push notification tokens, and, if you register with your Facebook account, your Facebook identifier.

_Log Information_ Our servers collect log files when you access our Services, including your browser type and language, access times, pages viewed, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the webpage or online service you visited before navigating to our Services. Additionally, we collect information about how you interact with our services, preferences expressed, and settings chosen. In some cases, we do this through the use of cookies, pixel tags, and similar technologies that create and maintain unique identifiers.

**Information Provided by Others**

Fetchr may combine the information collected from outside sources with other information in its possession.

_Third-party sources_ We may collect information from other sources including, user feedback, such as ratings or compliments, Fetchr business partners through which you create or access your Fetchr account, such as payment providers, social media services, on-demand music services, or apps or websites who use Fetchr’s APIs or whose API Fetchr uses; insurance providers; financial services providers; partner transportation companies;  and, the owner of an Fetchr for Business profile that you use, publicly available sources, and marketing service providers.

**_Information Sharing_**

_API and Integration Partner_ s If you connect to the Fetchr’s Digital Platform through an integration with a third party service, we may share information about your use of the Digital Platform with that third party. We may share your information with our third party partners in order to receive additional information about you. We may also share your information with third party partners to create offers that may be of interest to you.

_Third Party Services_ The Digital Platform may allow you to connect with other websites, products, or services that we don’t have control over (for example, we may give you the ability to order a food delivery from a restaurant from within the Fetchr App). If you use these services, we will provide the third party with information about you to allow them to provide the service to you (for example, we would give the restaurant your name, phone number and address to drop off the food). We can’t speak to the privacy practices of these third parties, and we encourage you to read their privacy policies before deciding whether to use their services.

_Analytics and Advertising Services_ We may allow other companies to use cookies, web beacons and other technologies on the Services that collect information about your use of the Services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Fetchr for analytics purposes, including to analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand your online activity.  Additionally, some companies may use the information they collect on certain areas of the Services to deliver targeted advertising on behalf of others.  For more information about interest-based ads, including how to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

_Other Sharing_ We may share your information with third parties in the following cases:

  * While negotiating or in relation to a change of corporate control such as a restructuring, merger or sale of our assets;
  * If a government authority requests information and we think disclosure is required or appropriate in order to comply with laws, regulations, or a legal process;
  * With law enforcement officials, government authorities, or third parties if we believe doing so is necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Fetchr community;
  * To comply with a legal requirement or process, including but not limited to, civil and criminal subpoenas, court orders or other compulsory disclosures;
  * If you signed up for a promotion with a promotion code, with your referrer to let them know about your redemption of or qualification for the promotion;
  * With our insurance partners to help determine and provide relevant coverage in the event of an incident;
  * To provide information about the use of the Digital Platform to potential business partners in aggregated or de-identified form that can’t reasonably be used to identify you; and,
  * Whenever you consent to the sharing.

**_Security_** _ _

We take reasonable measures to protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Fetchr retains your information while your account remains active, unless you ask us to delete your information or your account. Subject to the exceptions described below, Fetchr deletes or anonymizes your information upon request.

Subject to applicable law, Fetchr may retain information after account deletion if there is an unresolved issue relating to your account, such as an outstanding credit on your account or an unresolved claim or dispute. Moreover, Fetchr will retain information if required to do so by applicable law; and/or in aggregated and/or anonymized form. Fetchr may also retain certain information if necessary for its legitimate business interests, such as fraud prevention.

**_Your Choices_** ** _ _**

**Account Information**

You may update, correct or delete your online account information at any time by logging into your account. You can edit the name, phone number and email address associated with your account through the Settings menu in Fetchr App. You can also look up your deliveries history in the Fetchr App. If you delete any account information, we may retain certain information as detailed above.

**Device Permissions**

Most mobile platforms (iOS, Android, etc.) have defined certain types of device data that apps cannot access without your consent and these platforms have different permission systems for obtaining your consent. You can opt out of receiving push notifications through your device settings.

**Promotional Communications**

You may opt out of receiving marketing or promotional emails from us by following the instructions in those emails.  Please note that even if you opt out of receiving promotional emails, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations.

**Cookies**

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default.  If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to remove or reject cookies.  Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services.

**Contact Us**

Feel free to contact us at any time with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, our use and sharing practices, or your consent choices by contacting support@fetchr.us.
